

CONTACT

Phone : (+60) 10 7186943 Email : Adlinsaufi97@gmail.com Address : Cyberjaya, Selangor

SKILLS & COURSES

- Adobe Products
- Photoshop
- Premier Pro
- Illustrator
- After Effect
- Lightroom
- Microsoft Office
- Camera Handling
 Experienced in multiple cameras;
 Sony, Canon, Nikon
- Video Editing + Special Effects
- Production Management
 Writing script & storyboard
 Recording & directing
- Domestika
- Audiovisual Editing and Narrative for Short Films by Juanmi Cristóbal
- Documentary Filmmaking from Scratch by JRVISUALS

LANGUAGE

- English
- Malay



ACHIEVEMENTS

- Champions of Enactus Malaysia National Cup 2017 Matrade Exhibition Centre, Kuala Lumpur
- Second Runner Up of Enactus World Cup 2017 (Opening ExCel London, United Kingdom
- Director of AIESEC Global Village 2017

Muhammad

'ADLIN SAUFI

Bin Mohd Zamri

Graduated from Universiti Malaysia Sabah in Marine Science, but I have a lot of passion in creative productions both photography and video-making. Im now working in an IT & Resource company under the Communications Department as a Creative Media Producer whose in charges in productions of videos. Since coming in, I've established proper directions and mechanism for producing the content, and produced numbers of content which includes, podcasts, celebrations themed videos, video projects highlight and many more. Also have worked in EcoKnights, an environmental NGO at TTDI for almost 2 years as Junior Visual Communicator/ Junior arts director, in the Sustainability Department, as well as a photography and videography freelancer for more than 2 years.

Link to my portfolio

https://adlinzamri.myportfolio.com/



EXPERIENCES

Creative Media Producer, Rams Solutions Sdn Bhd

(Apr 2022 - current)

Provides and developed various kind of contents with objectives to increase brand awareness and brand appearance. In-charges & involves in most process from pre-production, production and editing processes.

Junior Visual Communicator, EcoKnights TTDI

(Aug 2020 - March 2022)

I am responsible for establishment of in-house production: KnightWatch Media and project highlights that we have been working on. Also produced several series including Sembang Alam Season 2 podcast, multiple contents to increase the engagement.

Freelance Photographer/Videographer, Divine Studio

(2017 - current)



EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science with Honours (Marine Science)

Universiti Malaysia Sabah (2016 -Now)

CGPA: 3.33

Foundation (Science Stream) Universiti Malaysia Sabah (2015 -2016) CGPA: 2.89

SPM (Science Stream)

Muzaffar Syah Science Secondary School (2010-2014)

6A, 2B+, 1B